question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named "
                 "Morgan Freeman.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Valve&#039;s &quot;Portal&quot; and &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchises exist within the same in-game universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
